I love you a lot!
我很愛你！
YUN TAE-O
（尹泰晤）
Hello?
喂？
Good morning.
早安
What?
什麼？
Open up.
幫我開門
What?!
不會吧！
Good morning, jagi.
早安，“jagi”
"Ja"?
“ja”？
A-Annyeonghaseyo.
“annyeonghaseyo”
Let me see your face.
讓我看看你的臉
I'm not wearing makeup.
可是我還沒化妝耶
My girlfriend is being so cute this morning.
我的女朋友一早就好可愛
Um, so, did you need something?
那個，你怎麼來了？
Right.
對了
I'm delivering your breakfast.
我是來送早餐來給侑里小姐的
After all, I'm your boyfriend.
畢竟我們是情侶啊
-I'm coming in. -What?
-我要進去囉 -什麼？
Um…
那個…
You actually made this for me?
你是特地做給我的嗎？
Yes, I'm your boyfriend, aren't I?
對，因為我是你的男友嘛
Thank you.
謝謝
I am your boyfriend, right?
我們是情侶對吧？
Hm?
什麼？
You and I are dating, right?
我們在交往沒錯吧？
Yes.
對
I wanted to hear those words.
這就是我想聽的
Would you say our first day as a couple was yesterday or today?
我們算是今天開始交往？ 還是昨天呢？
Um…
這個嘛…
Yesterday, I guess?
應該是昨天吧
That means today is our second day together.
那麼今天就是第二天囉
Tae-o.
泰晤
Want to go somewhere on our day off tomorrow?
明天休假要不要一起去哪裡玩？
Sure, how about Korea?
當然好，去韓國怎麼樣？
Korea? That's way too sudden.
韓國？這未免也太突然了
Is it?
是嗎？
Um, but…
那個，不過啊
I'd love to visit where you were born and raised someday.
我未來想去看看泰晤出生長大的地方
There is a park near my house with a beautiful view.
在我家附近，有一個風景漂亮的公園
If you yell your wish from there, it comes true.
在那裡喊出心願的話，就會實現
Then let's go yell out our wishes together, okay?
那我們找一天到那地方喊出心願吧
Yes, let's do that.
好，就這麼說定了
You're so pretty.
你真美
Let's eat.
那來吃飯吧
B-Before that,
在開動之前
I'll wash my face and brush my teeth.
我先去刷牙洗臉
-Wait. -Huh?
-等一下！ -怎麼了？
I'll brush them for you.
我來幫你刷牙吧
I'll brush them myself.
我自己來就可以
I'll do it.
我來刷
No.
不用了
-Are you embarrassed? -I'm not!
-你在害羞嗎？ -才沒有！
Is she embarrassed?
她果然在害羞呀？
So cute.
真可愛
If I win, you'll go to Kiritappu Cape.
如果我贏了，你就去霧多布岬
Go, Motomiya.
你就去吧，本宮
-Good morning. -Boss!
-早安 -社長！
Sorry about Hokkaido.
北海道的事真的很抱歉！
-Ouch! -It's fine. Don't push yourself.
-好痛！ -沒事吧？別勉強自己
-Okay. -Take a seat.
-好的 -你坐下吧
Sit down.
就坐著吧
Ouch.
好疼啊
Good morning.
早安
I compiled a report from our work trip. Take a look.
出差報告我整理好了，你確認一下
Sure.
好
And here are some souvenirs for your afternoon meetings.
另外這是想請你 帶去下午會議的伴手禮
Sure, thanks.
好，謝謝
And these are samples for our new spring products.
以及春天新產品的樣品
There's a mug.
這是馬克杯
-A mug. -And a tumbler.
-馬克杯 -對，還有保溫杯
-Tumbler. -And corks with a spring design.
-保溫杯 -還有春季設計的軟木杯墊，給你
-Okay. -And also,
-好 -另外就是
-there are gift boxes. -Okay.
-禮品組合 -知道了
-Check them by noon. -By noon?!
-你幫我在中午前確認好 -中午前？
Tell me if it's too much.
有困難再告訴我
I'll shift things around.
我會做調整
Noon. Got it.
明白了，中午前會確認完
-I'm sorry! Ouch! -It's okay.
-不好意思！好痛！ -沒關係，沒事的
Just sit.
我就叫你乖乖坐著了
Are you okay?
還好嗎？
Yeah, thanks.
我沒事，謝謝你
Thanks.
謝謝
This looks delicious!
看起來真好吃！
You finally made it to the avant-garde tonkotsu ramen place, Kame.
龜哥如願地來吃進化系豚骨拉麵了
Finally, tonkotsu for lunch.
咱終於可以在午餐吃到豚骨拉麵囉
Hurry, pass me the chopsticks.
-快點把筷子遞給我 -好
-Here you go, Tae-o. -Thank you.
-給你，泰晤 -謝謝
-Here. -Thanks.
-來 -謝啦
Enjoy your meal.
享用美食吧
LET'S EAT HERE
（下次一起來吃這個吧）
A heart.
愛心
Hm?
什麼？
Did you get a girlfriend?
你交到女朋友了？
No.
才沒有
What? "No"?
什麼？“沒有”？
Do you have something to hide?
有什麼需要隱瞞的嗎？
Nope.
不
It's fine. I found one.
沒有，的確如你所說的
I knew it. Congratulations!
我就知道，恭喜你！
Congratulations for what?
什麼事值得道賀啊？
Um…
我問你喔…
When you want to make special memories in Japan,
在日本想製造特別美好的回憶的話
where do you usually go on dates?
都會去哪裡約會？
You eat delicious food
一起去吃美食
or go to the beach.
或是去海邊
We've done both.
那些都做過了
In that case…
不然就是…
An oncheon?
“oncheon”？
-An oncheon, huh? -Yeah.
-“oncheon”啊？ -對
What's an oncheon?
“oncheon”是什麼意思？
Oncheons are oncheons.
“oncheon”就是“oncheon”哪
-Hot springs. -Are they tasty?
-“溫泉”啊 -那東西好吃嗎？
They're delicious.
簡直是極品
It's been a while, Park.
好久不見啊，朴
I would like to earnestly make a request.
有件事情想拜託你
There is something I would like you to procure.
我想請你幫我將某個東西拿到手
Good mor…ning.
早…
Did you put on makeup today?
你今天也沒化妝嗎？
Y-Yes.
是呀
She's so cute.
她好可愛
Time for the hot springs.
我們去泡溫泉吧
-Hot springs? -Yes.
-溫泉？ -對
We're going right now.
我們現在就去泡溫泉
Hot springs? Right now?
現在去泡溫泉？
Yes, the hot springs.
對，泡溫泉
SUPER BATHHOUSE
（超級澡堂 海獺城之湯）
Hot springs?
這算是溫泉？
Hot springs.
溫泉到了
-Let's go. -S-Sure.
-走吧 -好
They said we can choose any yukata here.
他們說可以選擇喜歡的浴衣
Hm?
什麼？
Oh, gwiyeowo means "cute."
哦，“gwiyeowo”是“可愛”的意思
Gwiyeowo.
“gwiyeowo”
Choose for me, Yuri.
那侑里小姐幫我選吧
What color would look good on me?
我適合什麼顏色呢？
What? Well…
我來選？我想想…
I think a bright color would suit you.
感覺你適合明亮的顏色
White, perhaps?
白色如何？
Gwiyeowo.
“gwiyeowo”
-Really? -Yes.
-真的嗎？ -真的
I'll wear white, then.
那我要白色的
But gray might be good too.
但灰色的也不錯
-I'll wear gray. -But blue…
-那就灰色 -不過藍色的也…
I'll wear blue.
那我要穿藍色的
Oh yeah, it's your birthday.
-是喔，畢竟是你生日嘛 -沒錯
Must be nice.
好羨慕喔
Can we meet today?
今天能見面嗎？
I can't.
沒辦法
Why?
為什麼？
READ
（已讀）
The spring tide is today.
因為是大潮
What?
什麼東西？
There's no hope.
我絕望了
Why am I always the only one in such despair?
就只有我一直陷入絕望之中
This is cute.
好可愛喔
-Hello? -When can you meet then?
-喂？ -那你到底什麼時候能見面？
-What? -And also,
-什麼？ -況且啊
what even is a spring tide?
“大潮”又是什麼鬼東西？
Would you like to go to the beach too then, Mahiro?
那真尋小姐也要去大海嗎？
What?
什麼？
I'd love to.
我很想去
What is happening?
這是要幹嘛？
We're harvesting sea slugs.
我們今天要抓海蛞蝓
Sea slugs?
海蛞蝓？
Sea slugs are found hiding in the rocks' shadows or in seaweed.
海蛞蝓會躲在岩石下面或是海藻之間
You can only harvest them during spring tides.
只有大潮的時候抓得到
Mahiro, you're lucky.
真尋小姐，你真幸運呢
What is it?
怎麼了嗎？
Oh, I couldn't read the letters.
哦，我看不懂字
That app is handy, isn't it?
好方便的應用程式啊
Yeah.
是啊
Do you want to enter the open-air baths together?
要一起泡露天溫泉嗎？
We can't, and I won't.
我們不能一起泡，我也不願意
We can't?
不可以嗎？
Well…
不過…
The stone sauna might be okay.
岩盤浴的話可以
Oh, I had trouble tying this.
天哪，這好難弄
Thank you.
謝謝
How does the yukata look on me?
浴衣適合我嗎？
It really suits you.
非常適合你
It suits you too.
侑里小姐也很搭呢
No.
不行
How about a ppoppo?
那可以“ppoppo”嗎？
What's a ppoppo?
“ppoppo”是什麼意思？
Look it up.
你查查看
Ppoppo.
“ppoppo”
PPOPPO KISS
（ppoppo 接吻）
We can't.
不可以啦
CAN I KISS YOU?
（我可以親你嗎？）
Don't be like this in public.
請別在人前做那種事
Well, then.
好吧
It's so hot.
好熱
It's Nishina! Nishina is here!
是仁科小姐！仁科小姐也在！
Come on.
走吧，我們出去
Let's go.
走了…
That was close.
好險啊
Huh?
怎麼了？
Shall we go home?
趁現在回去吧
What? We're leaving?
什麼？這麼早就要回去了嗎？
She'll find us, you know.
不然會被她看到啊
You think so?
是喔
Wait one second.
請等我一下
What do you think?
看起來怎麼樣？
It's cute.
好可愛
Really?
是嗎？
Wait one second.
等一下喔
Here.
來
So cute.
好可愛
-Come here. -Hm?
-過來 -幹嘛？
This was fun.
玩得真開心
-Really? -Yeah.
-真的嗎？ -對
Let's come again.
下次還想一起來
How about tomorrow then?
那明天要來嗎？
Tomorrow?
明天？
Tomorrow is…
明天有點…
Huh? Tae-o?
什麼？是泰晤嗎？
Oh, Nishina!
哦，是仁科小姐！
Is that your girlfriend?
難道那是你女友？
Yes.
對，是的
When I said hot springs, I didn't mean here.
我說的“溫泉”不是指這裡啦
What?
什麼？
Nice to meet you.
幸會啊
I work at the same company as Tae-o.
我是泰晤公司的同事
Oh, she's--
那個，我女朋友她…
What is she doing?
她在做什麼？
She gets shy easily.
她個性比較害羞
Oh, I see.
是喔，這樣啊
Sorry for interrupting.
抱歉打擾你們了
We'll be heading out first then.
那我們先走囉
Bye.
再見
Let's go.
走吧
Oh, well. I'm gonna have a beer.
算了，來喝啤酒吧
Excuse me.
我問你一件事
-Yes? -Did you give it some thought?
-什麼事？ -你想過了嗎？
The reason why I gave you the chocolate.
就是我給你巧克力的原因
I don't really understand
我搞不懂
what's going on in your mind or anything that you do.
你的想法或所做的一切
It's always too unpredictable to me.
對我來說都太難以捉摸了
That's my line.
那是我要說的台詞啦
What do I have to do
我到底要怎麼做
for you to notice me?
你才會在意我？
Notice you?
在意你？
May I?
可以嗎？
Yes.
可以
Did that
這樣做之後
help you notice me?
你有開始在意我嗎？
I'll forget that happened just now.
剛才的事我會忘掉的
What?
什麼？
The turnover time for human skin cells is around six weeks,
人類的皮膚細胞 更新週期大約是六週
while the lips only take three to four days.
嘴唇的細胞三、四天就會換新
So, in four days' time, it'll be as if it never happened.
也就是說四天後 就能當作什麼都沒發生
What are you talking about?
你那是什麼意思？
What about yourself?
我才想問你幹嘛這樣做！
You know how I feel, don't you?
你知道我的心意了吧
What? I don't understand at all.
什麼？我根本就搞不懂
You know that I like you, right?
我喜歡你！你看得出來吧？
What?
啥？
Huh?
什麼？
What?!
不會吧！
Nope.
不對
So cute.
真可愛
Peter Piper picked a peck of pickled peppers.
和尚端湯上塔堂 塔滑湯灑湯燙塔，換你
Peter Piper picked a peck of…
和尚端湯上塔堂，塔“話”湯灑…
peppered pickles.
湯燙“他”
Peppered pickles?
湯燙“他”？
-Peppered? -Dang it!
-“他”？ -可惡啊！
Heard of it before?
你知道這個嗎？
I think I have.
我應該知道喔
The daruma fell over.
一、二、三，木頭人
Daruma?
“木頭人”？
Yeah, it falls over.
對，要學木頭人不能動
Let's try it.
我們來玩玩看
All right.
好
Here we go.
開始吧
The daruma…
一、二、三…
fell over!
木頭人！
The daruma fell over.
一、二、三，木頭人！
Ppoppo?
“ppoppo”？
Ppoppo.
“ppoppo”
PPOPPO KISS
（ppoppo 接吻）
The daruma fell over!
一、二、三，木頭人！
"Ppoppo haedo dwae"?
“ppoppo haedo dwae”？
Huh?
什麼意思？
The daruma fell over!
一、二、三，木頭人！
"Han"?
“han”？
One more time?
再一次好嗎？
What?
什麼？
It's Mahiro.
是真尋打來的
Hello?
喂？
He rejected me!
我被他甩了！
What?
什麼？
Like I said,
我是說…
the doctor
我被那個博士
rejected me!
狠狠甩了啦！
What?!
不會吧？
I can't believe this!
真的太離譜了！
Who would actually get rejected at the beach in the winter?
怎麼會有人在冬天的海邊被甩啦？
Um…
我問一下…
What happened exactly?
究竟發生什麼事了？
Could it be
難不成…
that you really didn't know?
你真的不明白？
Yes.
對
Were you
我確認一下
-referring to romantic feelings-- -Yes.
-你對我有戀愛的感覺… -沒錯
When could that have happened?
是什麼時候開始的？
I…
我…
have never seen you in that way.
從來沒有把你當成是戀愛對象
I'm sorry.
真的很抱歉
I've never been rejected before.
這是我人生頭一次被甩
Never?
頭一次？
That's impressive.
真厲害
Have you ever been rejected?
侑里小姐有被甩過嗎？
I have.
有啊
Was it
是你先前說過的
your ex-boyfriend from high school?
那個高中的前男友？
Yeah.
對
-Why? -Huh?
-為什麼？ -什麼？
It's fine if you don't want to say.
不想說就不用說沒關係
Sorry.
抱歉
I don't care either way.
不想說也無所謂
You're always like this, Yuri.
侑里小姐，你總是這樣
Hm?
什麼意思？
You always evade the topic
重要的事都會蒙混過去
and look away.
然後迴避視線
I know you're bearing something.
我知道你有煩惱的事
I thought you'd tell me one day,
我以為有天你會願意說出來
but in the end,
結果到頭來
you're never going to tell me, huh?
你是打算永遠都不說出口吧？
I'm sorry.
對不起
I apologize, I got too emotional.
不好意思，我現在情緒有點激動
I'll take my leave now.
我今天就先回去了
I…
我…
can hear other people's thoughts.
能夠聽到別人內心的想法
What?
什麼？
What do you mean?
這是什麼意思？
When I lock eyes with someone,
只要看著對方的眼睛
I can hear what that person is thinking.
我就能聽到對方在想什麼
Why are you suddenly turning this into a magical fantasy?
為何突然扯到那種奇幻設定？
Sorry, it's hard to believe, right?
抱歉，你很難相信吧？
Does she not want to tell me the truth that badly?
她就這麼不願意告訴我真相？
No.
不是的
It's true.
這就是真相
What?
什麼？
I'm sorry.
抱歉
But…
可是…
I can hear everything.
我就是能聽見
Seriously?
真的假的？
Seriously.
是真的
Good evening.
晚安
-Annyeong… -…haseyo.
-“annyeong…” -“haseyo”
Gamsa…
“gamsa…”
…habnida.
“hapnida”
Sarang…
“sarang…”
…haeyo.
“haeyo”
This…
這不是…
can't be real.
真的吧？
I'm sorry.
抱歉啊
When did it start?
什麼時候開始的？
By the time we met,
從我們認識的時候
I was already…
就是這樣子
That's scary.
好可怕
You know, I can hear people's thoughts.
我可以聽到人們內心的想法
People's thoughts?
內心的想法？
That's scary.
好恐怖啊
I apologize, I think I'll have to leave for today.
不好意思，我今天還是先回去了
Is Senpai out today?
學長請假嗎？
He says he has a fever from overthinking.
他說是因為用腦過度發燒
I wonder what happened to Onoda.
不知道小野田是怎麼了
Overthinking?
用腦過度而發燒？
The person Tae-o likes isn't Mahiro.
泰晤喜歡的人不是真尋小姐
It's the company CEO.
對方好像是公司的社長
Overthinking…
用腦過度…
Um…
那個…
-Tae-o. -Yes?
-泰晤啊 -是
Um, it's about the person you like.
我問你喔，你喜歡的人
Is it true that she's the CEO?
真的是那個社長嗎？
Yes.
沒錯
But your heart was broken, yes?
但你不是失戀了嗎？
Actually…
其實…
she became my girlfriend!
我們變成情侶了！
What is the meaning of this?
這是怎麼回事？
Today is our fourth day.
今天是我們交往的第四天
You're kidding.
不會吧
This can't be.
絕不能有這種事
Why not?
為什麼？
Because…
因為…
Do you…
你知道…
know everything about her?
她的一切嗎？
Everything?
一切？
There may be something you have yet to know about her.
關於她，可能還有些你不知道的事
What do you mean?
這是什麼意思？
Could you please
你要不要重新考慮一下
reconsider dating her?
跟她交往的事？
Tae-o, you…
泰晤，你啊…
are like a son to me.
就等同我的孩子
I'll be going now.
我要回去了
Kame, you're up.
龜哥，請說吧
You messed up.
不對喔
That's hard. Try it.
好難喔，你試一下
-Wow. What? -Thank you.
好猛喔，什麼？
What does ganjang mean?
“ganjang”是什麼意思？
Ganjang gongjang means
“ganjang gongjang”
soy sauce factory.
是“醬油工廠”
Good morning.
早安
-Good morning.
-早啊 -早安
Kame, one more try.
龜哥，再來一次
-No, there's no "doenjang." -Totally wrong.
-不對，不是“doenjang” -完全扯不上邊
Wait, what?
等等，是嗎？
Ganjang gongjang.
“ganjang gongjang”
Now I get it.
我懂了
-Once more. -Got it.
-你再說一次 -包在我身上
Ganjang gongjang jonjang janggo. How's that?
“ganjang gongjang jonjang janggo”對嗎？
-It's not jonjang janggo. -I was so close.
-不是“jonjang janggo” -可惜啊
-That was close. -It was, right?
-只差一點 -是啊，我差點說對了吧？
Why did I tell her?
我為什麼要說出來？
Not ganjo. Ganjang.
並非“ganjo”，是“ganjang”
Try again, Kame.
“ganjang”，龜哥，再一次
-Not gonjang janggo. -Totally wrong.
-不是“gonjang janggo” -全都錯了嘛
What's with that tone?
你什麼意思哪？
Seriously? This tastes awful.
這什麼東西？有夠難吃
What would you do if I said I'm from the future.
如果我說我來自未來，你會怎麼樣？
What?
什麼？
What would you do?
你會怎麼做？
Should I reply seriously?
你要我認真回答你那種問題？
Don't you think
你會不會…
it would be scary?
覺得我很可怕？
Not sure.
不確定耶
Even now, you're already pretty mysterious to me, Mahiro.
對我來說，真尋現在 也是未知的生物啊
It's scary.
我會怕怕的
What?
什麼？
The way you always start nonsensical conversations like this,
你會突然提起莫名其妙的話題
or how your emotions are always gushing out,
感情經常表現出來
is hard for me to understand.
那些我都無法理解
I often think it's scary.
有時甚至還覺得可怕呢
Are you picking a fight?
你是想跟我吵架嗎？
I'm just answering your question.
我只是回答了問題
What are you trying to say?
也太難懂了
I'm just saying
意思就是說
that regardless of whether you came from the future or not,
不管你是來自未來或任何地方
you're still Mahiro to me.
對我來說，你就是你啊
Oh, Boss.
哦，社長
Yuri.
侑里小姐
What is it?
怎麼了？
I'll go home with you,
一起回去吧
since we're dating.
畢竟我們在交往嘛
Are you hungry?
你肚子餓不餓？
Yeah.
嗯
-Did something happen? -Hm?
-發生什麼事了嗎？ -什麼？
You seem down.
你看起來沒有精神
No, I'm fine.
沒那回事啦
Say whatever you want.
你可以告訴我任何事
I'll…
就由我…
give you some energy!
帶給你滿滿的精神！
Sorry.
抱歉
Don't say sorry.
不要對我道歉
Why are you feeling down?
告訴我你無精打采的理由吧
Mahiro and I…
我跟真尋…
…had a fight?
吵架了嗎？
Not a fight, but…
與其說是吵架…
Did you talk through everything properly?
你有把心裡想的通通說出來嗎？
Yuri, you're hard to understand…
侑里小姐比較難懂…
And people usually don't know what others are thinking.
人通常不能理解別人的心
In that moment, you told me upfront
你當時坦率地將感情表達給我
that you like me.
說你喜歡我
I was really happy.
我真的很高興
That was…
那是因為…
only because you said it to me upfront.
泰晤對我坦白說出了心意
How about Mahiro?
那真尋小姐呢？
Mahiro is always upfront too, isn't she?
真尋小姐平常也都很直率吧？
It's okay.
沒事的
I'm here for you.
有我陪著你
As for dinner together, let's push it to tomorrow.
明天再一起吃飯好了
Go.
那麼去吧
Yeah.
好
Thank you.
謝謝
I'll be off.
那我走了
Get there safely.
路上小心
Mahiro?
真尋？
I'm sorry…
很抱歉…
for scaring you.
讓你害怕了
I should be the one apologizing.
該道歉的是我才對
Please.
拜託
Open your eyes.
請你睜開眼睛
I ran away earlier…
上次我從你面前逃跑…
and hurt you, Yuri.
還深深傷害了侑里小姐
I'm sorry.
對不起
It's because I told you so suddenly.
都怪我突然對你說出實情
But I'm the one who made you tell me.
但是我逼你說出口的
-No, I-- -It was me.
-不，是我… -是我的錯！
You always blame yourself like that.
侑里小姐每次都這樣責備自己
You're always thinking of others
時時刻刻都顧慮著周遭的人
and being considerate.
總是在替別人著想
No.
不是的
That's not it.
並不是那樣
To be honest…
其實…
It's because I was afraid you would be scared of me.
我是怕你會覺得我很恐怖
I mean,
因為…
you were thinking you're scared, right?
你曾在心裡覺得我很可怕吧？
I wouldn't get to ask for your advice anymore,
一想到今後有事也不能找你商量
or eat lunch with you,
不能再跟你去吃午餐
or be friends with you,
不能再自稱是你的朋友
or listen to your pointless stories.
不能再聽到你說那些無聊的瑣碎小事
Losing all of that scared me.
就讓我感到非常害怕
So, the reason why I couldn't open up to you
我之所以無法對你坦白
was for my benefit.
都只是為了我自己
I knew it.
果然啊
You are you, and that's all there is to it.
侑里小姐還是我所認識的侑里小姐
You love me, don't you?
你明明就很喜歡我嘛
It's fine.
沒關係
It's fine, even if you're from the future.
即使你來自未來，我也不在乎
You haven't told Tae-o, right?
反正你還沒跟泰晤說吧？
No.
對
You don't have to.
不用說也沒關係
Friends and lovers are different.
戀人跟朋友不一樣
So…
所以啊…
I'll protect you.
我會保護你的
Wait, you just called my stories pointless.
等等，你剛剛提到 我說的話很無聊吧？
They are pointless.
是無聊的瑣事沒錯啊
I like that about you.
但我就是喜歡聽嘛
Huh?
什麼？
You told Mahiro?
你跟真尋說了？
Yes, I was finally able to tell her.
對，終於能說出口了
I see.
我知道了
Isn't that great?
那是一件好事呢
Someone gave me a push from behind.
有人在背後鼓勵我
Oh, really?
是嗎？
Dad, I…
爸爸，我…
found someone I like.
我有喜歡的人了
Huh?
什麼？
I'm dating him now.
我跟那個人開始交往了
What?! Wh-What kind of person is he?
真的嗎？是怎樣的人？
He's a kind person.
他溫柔又體貼
What? Is that so.
是嗎？這樣啊
I see.
原來是這樣…
Congratulations, Yuri.
恭喜你，侑里
I see…
是喔！
You're too happy about this.
你開心過頭了啦
I'm glad you two made up.
你們能和好真是太好了
Yeah, it's all thanks to you. Thank you.
是啊，這都是你的功勞，謝謝
Now we can finally
我們終於能夠
have dinner together.
一起吃晚餐了
It's been a while, huh?
很久沒一起吃了吧？
Was Hokkaido the last time?
上次是在北海道？
But Hanaoka was there at the time.
可是那時候花岡先生也在
When was the last time we had a meal with just the two of us?
最後一次單獨吃晚餐是什麼時候？
I think…
我記得是…
Oh, right.
是啊，沒錯
That place was tasty. We should go again…
那間店很好吃，下次再一起…
Hm?
嗯？
When was it again?
是什麼時候來著？
I like you, Yuri.
雖然我喜歡你，侑里
But I don't think we can continue this.
但我無法繼續跟你交往
I'm sorry.
對不起
Yuri.
侑里小姐
If he finds out…
如果他知道了事實…
we may never look at each other again.
那我也許就不能再看著他的眼睛
He is the only one…
唯獨對他…
The daruma…
一、二、三…
He can never know.
我一定要瞞到底
…fell over.
木頭人
Yuri.
侑里
-Green onions.
-蔥
-Chives.
-韭菜
-Spinach.
-菠菜
-Tofu.
-豆腐
-Potatoes.
-馬鈴薯
I forgot the potatoes.
我忘記馬鈴薯了
-I'll go buy them. -I'll go too.
-我去買來 -那我一起去
-Head back first. -What?
-你先回去吧 -什麼？
BEST BIBIMBAP EVER. I FEEL ENERGIZED. THANK YOU.
（這是我吃過最好吃的韓式拌飯 成功補給了能量，謝謝你）
Min Ha-na.
“閔荷娜”
Professor, someone named Park sent you a package.
教授，一位朴的人寄包裹給你
Thank you.
謝謝
"The Girl Who Can Hear…"
“《能聽見你心聲的…》”
"Your Heart…"
“《少女》”
THE GIRL WHO CAN HEAR YOUR HEART
（《能聽見你心聲的少女》）
"Hear us. Hear us."
“‘聽我們說…’
"The animals looked into the girl's eyes
動物們注視著少女的眼睛
and pleaded in their hearts."
並在內心說道
"This girl has a special power."
因為少女擁有特殊的能力
"When she locks eyes with another,
那個能力就是在互相對望時
only then can she hear the voice in their heart."
她可以聽到對方的心聲”
What?
什麼？
"One day, the girl met a boy with a kind heart."
“有天少女遇見了少年 他擁有一顆溫柔的心
"The boy showed a great amount of love to the girl."
少年向少女傳達了許多愛意
"And the two confirmed their love for each other."
最終兩人確認了彼此的愛”
"However, the girl kept her power to hear people's hearts
“但是這名少女並未將擁有 能聽到心聲能力的事
as a secret from the boy."
告訴少年
"In the end, the two of them
在最後有各種不幸
were met with much misfortune."
發生在兩人身上
"That was the fate given to the girl who could hear
對於能聽見心聲的少女
people's hearts."
這便是上天賦予她的命運”
What is this?
這是怎麼回事？
Subtitle translation by: Chul Woong Kim
字幕翻譯：陳盈華
I am incredibly happy right now.
我現在非常幸福
Get energized!
能量補給！
If you could get rid of that power…
如果能消除那種能力…
In that case, Dad and I…
那我就不能再跟爸爸…
Are you prepared for this?
你做好覺悟了嗎？